<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: bible | Godliness]]></title>
  <link href="http://jicesnow.github.com/blog/categories/bible/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://jicesnow.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2012-04-01T01:28:52+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://jicesnow.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jicesnow]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[哥林多前书－第13章]]></title>
    <link href="http://jicesnow.github.com/blog/2012/03/31/corinthians-13/"/>
    <updated>2012-03-31T17:13:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://jicesnow.github.com/blog/2012/03/31/corinthians-13</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h4>13:4    [hgb]   爱 是 恒 久 忍 耐 ， 又 有 恩 慈 。 爱 是 不 嫉 妒 。 爱 是 不 自 夸 。 不 张 狂 。</h4>

<blockquote><p>[kjv]  Charity suffereth long, and is kind; charity envieth not; charity vaunteth not itself, is not puffed up;</p>

<p>[bbe]  Love is never tired of waiting; love is kind; love has no envy; love has no high opinion of itself, love has no pride;</p></blockquote>

<h4>13:5    [hgb]   不 作 害 羞 的 事 。 不 求 自 己 的 益 处 。 不 轻 易 发 怒 。 不 计 算 人 的 恶 。</h4>

<blockquote><p>[kjv]  Doth not behave itself unseemly, seeketh not her own, is not easily provoked, thinketh no evil;</p>

<p>[bbe]  Love's ways are ever fair, it takes no thought for itself; it is not quickly made angry, it takes no account of evil;</p></blockquote>

<h4>13:6    [hgb]   不 喜 欢 不 义 。 只 喜 欢 真 理 。</h4>

<blockquote><p>[kjv]  Rejoiceth not in iniquity, but rejoiceth in the truth;</p>

<p>[bbe]  It takes no pleasure in wrongdoing, but has joy in what is true;</p></blockquote>

<h4>13:7    [hgb]   凡 事 包 容 。 凡 事 相 信 。 凡 事 盼 望 。 凡 事 忍 耐 。</h4>

<blockquote><p>[kjv]  Beareth all things, believeth all things, hopeth all things, endureth all things.</p>

<p>[bbe]  Love has the power of undergoing all things, having faith in all things, hoping all things.</p></blockquote>

<h4>13:8    [hgb]   爱 是 永 不 止 息 。 先 知 讲 道 之 能 ， 终 必 归 于 无 有 。 说 方 言 之 能 ， 终 必 停 止 ， 知 识 也 终 必 归 于 无 有 。</h4>

<blockquote><p>[kjv]  Charity never faileth: but whether there be prophecies, they shall fail; whether there be tongues, they shall cease; whether there be knowledge, it shall vanish away.</p>

<p>[bbe]  Though the prophet's word may come to an end, tongues come to nothing, and knowledge have no more value, love has no end.</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
